RETINDER LABANA

OBJECTIVE

To obtain a customer service position at Scotiabank where I can maximize my people oriented experience, communication skills and my problem analysis and problem solving abilities.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Expert in customer care/communications, problem solving and relationship building. Proficient with computer software applications including Microsoft Word, Excel, and other Microsoft Office programs.

Programming knowledge in Java, C#, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JSON, AJAX, and XML.

Developed web applications using responsive design with CSS3, openweathermaps.org API and google maps api.

Experience with software development lifecycle, and methodologies. Experience in developing software in traditional environment with Waterfall and agile environment using Scrum. Excellent communication skills. Fluent in English, Hindi and Punjabi.

EXPERIENCE

SUMMER INTERNSHIP, COGNIZANT TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS

15th July 2013 - 21st August 2013

During the program I worked on accounting concepts, revenue and cost projections, Interest and receivables, calculation of assets, liabilities and amortization amongst other things. I also developed a high-level understanding of business model and operations of IT service industry and helped in creation of a business plan for starting a new IT project.

PARAMOUNT FINE FOODS

May 2016 – August 2016 Line Cook

EDUCATION

RYERSON UNIVERSITY – TORONTO, ONTARIO – BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

 ${\sf CARDINAL\ AMBROZIC\ CATHOLIC\ S.S-BRAMPTON,\ ONTARIO-HIGH\ SCHOOL\ DIPLOMA}$

Achieved OSSD

COMMUNICATION

Advertising charity events for Guru Garib Niwaj Nirmal Seva (Charity for the education of the children in India). Where I handled budget and time management with positive attitude and behavior.

WICS (WOMAN IN COMPUTER SCIENCE)

October 2016 - present

Depute Events

RISA (RYERSON INDIAN STUDENT ACCOSIATION)

September 2016 - present

VP Marketing

LEADERSHIP

Hosting high school events as group leader and Event Assistant, where I had and an opportunity to strengthen my leadership and management skills.

Hosting WICS events

- Cookies and Coco Cram night
- Meet and Greet

CURRENT PROJECTS

Making a web application game (2 month project) Geographical location website

REFERENCES

REFERENCES AVALIBLE UPON REQUEST